<?xml version="1.0"?>
<article id="2">
    <headline>Microsoft</headline>
    <author>test</author>
    <date>20.05.2021</date>
    <email>test@gmail.com</email>
    <keywords>
        <keyword number="1">microsoft</keyword>
        <keyword number="2">bethesda</keyword>
        <keyword number="3">conference</keyword>
    </keywords>
    <abstract>Will we finally get our first proper look at Starfield?</abstract>
    <Intro>The E3 season, or whatever it's called these days, is rapidly closing in.
          Geoff Keighley's Summer Game Fest gets the ball rolling on June 10, followed
          by the online-only E3 from June 12-15, and individual events like Ubisoft Forward,
          EA Play Live, and of course the PC Gaming Show and Future Games Show.</Intro>
    <Main>Microsoft and Bethesda will also return with online presentations this year, 
         and according to a Le Figaro report (via VGC), this year they'll be doing a joint event.
         Specifics weren't revealed, although Matt Booty, head of Microsoft Studios
         (and thus a guy who's in a good position to know about these things) said it will take place in a few weeks,
         dropping it right into the meaty part of the Big Summer o' Games.
         A shared showcase makes sense. Microsoft owns Bethesda now, in case that had slipped your mind, and while Bethesda
         has historically done its own thing (and certainly remains big enough to continue doing so), it's a big jewel in the
         Xbox crown. Rolling Bethesda's showcase into a larger Xbox event is a great opportunity to make a statement, especially if,
         as many expect, it will include a look at Starfield and possibly a release date tease. </Main>
    <Conclusion>Starfield is expected to be Bethesda's next big thing it's the studio's first original RPG in 25 years
                and recent rumors indicate that it will not be released on the PlayStation 5. I've reached out to Microsoft and Bethesda
                to confirm their reported plans for a joint show, and will update if I receive a reply. You can keep track of all of the online
                events happening this summer with our handy E3 2021 schedule.</Conclusion>
</article>
